all right good afternoon everybody my
好的，大家下午好
name is Rob salt I'm the chair man of
我叫罗伯·索尔特（Rob Salt）
the Apache maven project and I'm going
Apache Maven项目，我要去
to talk about the work I've done for
谈论我所做的工作
supporting Java 940 but you may have
支持Java 940，但您可能拥有
project this quotes the success of Java
这个项目引用了Java的成功
9 depends on the adoption by IDs and
9取决于ID和
build tools like maven is well it's not
像maven这样的构建工具不是
actually only for Java 9 but it would be
实际上仅适用于Java 9，但是
for every Java version but in this case
对于每个Java版本，但在这种情况下
Java 9 comes with so much new features
Java 9拥有许多新功能
that this is probably very very
这可能是非常非常
important so when did it all start it
重要，所以什么时候开始
all started in 2004 13 with the first
始于2004年13
releases of Java 9 and in 2015 they came
Java 9发行版，并在2015年发布
with the jigsaw early access releases
拼图的抢先体验版本
the jigsaw early access release is a zip
拼图的抢先体验版本是zip
file and it's just a matter of unpacking
文件，这只是解压缩的问题
it and putting it on your system the
并将其放在您的系统上
other one the other one G of 9 1 is is a
另一个9 9 1的另一个G是一个
wizard and it will be the new default of
向导，它将是的新默认设置
your system so for that reason I prefer
您的系统，因此我更喜欢
to use the jigsaw so we have challenge
使用拼图，所以我们面临挑战
and we say that we want to support Java
我们说我们要支持Java
9 with maven 3 todo
9与Maven 3 Todo
right now we are made at maven 3.3 the
现在我们在Maven 3.3
ninth and we only want to support the of
第九，我们只想支持
9 by upgrading the plugins so that's our
9通过升级插件，这就是我们的
challenge
挑战
I'll be how can you test that well a
我将要如何测试一下
standard upgrade is use specify the Java
标准升级是使用指定Java
home and you point it to the JDK 9 you
家，您将它指向JDK 9
verify the source and target is in this
验证源和目标在此
case because Java 9 the minimum
案例，因为Java 9最低
supported version is for source and
受支持的版本适用于源代码和
target is 6 so if you have a Java 5
目标是6，所以如果您有Java 5
projects you will have to use a fork and
项目，您将不得不使用叉子和
refer to a different jdk so this also
参考不同的jdk，所以这也
means that the runtime of maven doesn't
意味着Maven的运行时不会
have to be exactly the same as the JDK
必须与JDK完全相同
used by the maven compiler plugin one of
由maven编译器插件之一使用
the most interesting things when doing
做时最有趣的事情
this for us was depth 260 it's about
对我们来说这是深度260
encapsulating most in internal API so if
大部分封装在内部API中，因此
Nathan would run it would kind of proof
内森（Nathan）将运行它会证明
that we are not using any internal api's
我们没有使用任何内部api
so what happened so far the first Java
所以到目前为止，第一个Java发生了什么
9e early access release that's the one
9e抢先体验版就是其中之一
which started in 2014 we had close to no
从2014年开始，我们几乎没有
issues there was one about system
关于系统的问题
properties in combination with null
属性结合null
values but that was restored quite fast
值，但恢复得很快
and nobody not a lot of projects had
没有很多项目
issues with that however the first
问题，但是第一个
jigsaw early access release about 99% of
拼图的抢先体验版约占99％
the Java maven projects failed to
Java Maven项目失败
compile so in the beginning we I when I
这样一开始我们就编译
noticed this I thought it was may have a
注意到这我以为可能有一个
core issue but it wasn't it was actually
核心问题，但实际上不是
caused by the Java 2 provider in
由Java 2提供程序在
combination with the system class loader
与系统类加载器结合
we are not using the Java executable to
我们没有使用Java可执行文件来
compile code we are using the Java tool
编译我们正在使用Java工具的代码
provider so we can do it with Java
提供程序，因此我们可以使用Java来实现
itself
本身
so this was fixed and released within 72
因此，此问题已在72秒内修复并发布
hours and up until now we had to change
几个小时直到现在我们不得不改变
zero lines of code in Mayville core just
Mayville核心中的零行代码
to run on Java 9
在Java 9上运行
about 10% of the jobs are related to
大约10％的工作与
maven and this is a list of the related
Maven，这是相关列表
jobs the session is too short to handle
会话太短而无法处理的作业
them all so this will be the agenda and
他们所有，所以这将是议程，
let's start with the utf8 property files
让我们从utf8属性文件开始
so especially for Europeans which are
所以特别是对于
familiar with special character sets you
熟悉特殊字符集
can know that sometimes you get very
知道有时候你会变得非常
weird characters in the output and this
输出中的怪异字符
should solve that so let's see suppose
应该解决这个问题，让我们来看一下
we have this kind of file in this case
在这种情况下，我们有这种文件
this this e is translated by by eclipse
这个e由eclipse翻译
correctly but it all depends on the
正确，但这完全取决于
editor you are using if that this is
您正在使用的编辑器，如果这是
still this kind of e the proper way to
仍然是这种正确的方法
do it is to escape it like this so in
这样做是为了逃脱它，所以在
this case we can run it like this and
在这种情况下，我们可以像这样运行它
above you see the result of Java 8 and
在上方，您会看到Java 8的结果，
below Java line and this is ISO based
在Java行下方，这是基于ISO的
properties files so now let's do it with
属性文件，现在让我们来做
utf-8
utf-8
you see the this church for those who
你看到这个教堂的人
are familiar with utf-8 and all kinds of
熟悉utf-8和各种
things
东西
if this run and CODIS you will get
如果运行此命令和CODIS，您将获得
always something like this but you will
总是这样，但是你会
see that with JDK 9 it will not be
看到使用JDK 9不会
accepted no problem
接受没问题
next is about the new version string
接下来是关于新版本的字符串
scheme yesterday Allen bayman already
计划昨天艾伦贝曼已经
told that this has a huge impact on the
告诉这对
whole system all projects using it in
整个系统中使用它的所有项目
our case we are using several system
我们的案例，我们正在使用几个系统
properties system properties so in the
属性系统属性，因此在
middle you see the original version
中间你看到的是原始版本
schemes
方案
and on the right you see deeper posts so
在右侧，您会看到更深的帖子，因此
why is this an issue what we do is we do
为什么这是一个问题我们要做的是我们要做的
a version and dot split and take the
一个版本和点拆分，并采取
second argument and in that case you
第二个参数，在这种情况下，您
will get the index out of bound
将使索引超出范围
index exception so in case you see
索引异常，以防万一
something like this there's probably
像这样的东西
something wrong with the version so this
版本有问题，所以这
has already been solved in several
已经解决了几个
projects so then this issue is in maven
项目，那么这个问题就在专家
archiver
封存者
and fixed in 3.1 and almost every
并固定在3.1和几乎每个
packaging plug-in depends on it so the
包装插件取决于它，因此
major are three dots oh it's ready
主要是三个点哦，准备好了
released exactly the same for the maven
释放的行家完全一样
war plug-in and maven air plugin will be
war插件和maven air插件将
released soon with including this fix
很快发布，包括此修复程序
also the maven Java plug-in is already
而且Maven Java插件已经存在
fixed and maybe there are more but we
固定，也许还有更多，但我们
have to hit this issue yes
必须打这个问题是
next jack is about compiled for all the
下一个杰克将为所有
platform versions the issue here is that
平台版本这里的问题是
in some cases it can lead leak classes
在某些情况下，它可能导致泄漏等级
from the jdk the official requirements
从jdk官方要求
to run a Java of Java C is with both
同时运行Java和Java C
source target but also the boot class
源目标，以及启动类
path and I'm pretty sure that nobody
路径，我很确定没有人
does it even we add it maybe we don't do
即使我们添加它也可能不这样做吗
it because we have other solutions for
这是因为我们还有其他解决方案
it but this is the official way to
但这是官方的方式
ensure that your codes will be compiled
确保您的代码将被编译
and will also run at runtime so let's
并且还将在运行时运行，所以让我们
see the problem
看到问题
so here we have a bit of coat
所以这里有一些外套
like this and we say it's Java 6 it
这样，我们说它是Java 6
should be Java 6 cot it should run on
应该是Java 6 cot，应该在其上运行
that what it's using laptop eclipse
那是使用笔记本电脑的日食
already recognizes that this is an issue
已经意识到这是一个问题
but it comes with something interesting
但它带有一些有趣的东西
it says comfort to anonymous class so
它说对匿名班很安慰
let's do that
让我们做
I think I did it that's okay
我想我做到了，没关系
projects
专案
okay there we have the error again
好的，我们再次遇到错误
it's used to work
它曾经工作
okay I can do it it's not problem if I
好吧，我可以做到，如果我没问题
just say in this case and for 40 example
只是说在这种情况下，例如40
it doesn't take here so in this case I
这里不需要，所以在这种情况下，我
will save it but this stream method is
将保存它，但是此流方法是
introduced in Java it's the same as for
用Java引入的与
each so even though we say that this
即使我们说这个
should be Java 6 code with with these
这些应该是Java 6代码
Java 8 methods it's not complaining so
Java 8方法不抱怨
here we go may have clean compile of
我们可以在这里进行干净的编译
this class
这节课
it says bill success
它说法案成功
if I am going to run this with Java 7
如果我要用Java 7运行它
again Mavenlink by now it recognizes the
现在，Mavenlink再次认识到
compilation failure by the way discolour
编译失败的方式变色
thinks this is a new feature in the next
认为这是下一个新功能
version of maven so I'm using it here
版本的Maven，所以我在这里使用它
for the demo so this is the real issue
对于演示，这是真正的问题
we have several methods which are only
我们只有几种方法
known in Java 8 and when you compile it
在Java 8中以及在编译时已知
with Java 8 it's not recognized the
与Java 8不能识别
first mavis solution that's already
第一个mavis解决方案已经
there is to use the maven toolchain
有使用Maven工具链
plugin with the with this plugin you can
带有的插件，您可以
specify the JDK switch are installed in
指定将JDK开关安装在
your system the tool chain XML can be
您的系统的工具链XML可以是
placed on two places one is equation is
放在两个地方一个是等式
in the bottom two folder and since May
在底部的两个文件夹中，自5月以来
3.3 that one it's also available in Econ
3.3在Econ中也可用
folder of the amazing distribution
惊人的发行文件夹
the other solution is to use the animals
另一个解决方案是使用动物
never maven plugin
从不Maven插件
it's called animals sniffer because of
因为它被称为动物嗅探器
the code name used for earlier versions
早期版本使用的代号
of Java so we have for instance tiger
Java的例子，例如老虎
mustang dolphin and based on that ID we
野马海豚，根据该ID，我们
have had created the animal sniffer so
创造了动物嗅探器，所以
you have here a signature and that
你在这里有签名
contains all the classes and methods
包含所有类和方法
used only for death and JRE and now with
仅用于死亡和JRE，现在用于
a Java 9 there is a new solution there's
Java 9有一个新的解决方案
- release actually since the latest
-实际上从最新版本发布
jigsaw is - - release and that's exactly
拼图是--释放，这就是
the same as saying this source and -
就像说这个来源一样-
target and that bootless path for em
目标和em的无引导路径
you can figure can't configure it like
你可以认为它无法像
this just at the release deck with a
这只是在发布平台上
specific version but you can also use a
特定版本，但您也可以使用
property may have not compile the
属性可能尚未编译
release and if you have both source and
发布，如果您同时拥有来源和
target and release specified then
然后指定目标和释放
release will win so let's see so now I'm
发布将获胜，所以让我们现在就来看
going to compile with a tool change I
我要用工具更改进行编译
have edited in this case to profile as
在这种情况下已编辑为
you can see I'm running it with Java 8
你可以看到我正在用Java 8运行它
the one which wasn't complaining about
没有抱怨的那个
this this compilation failure and here
这个编译失败的地方
you see the tool change picks up version
您会看到工具更换的版本
in this case Java 7 because that's the
在这种情况下，Java 7是因为
one I've installed on my system you also
我已经在系统上安装了一个
see that the medical pilot plug-in will
看到医学飞行员插件会
use this from tool chain and it's using
从工具链中使用它，并且正在使用
again Java 7 and we already saw it
再次使用Java 7，我们已经看到了
before that when you compile this with
在此之前，您使用
Java 7 it will have a compilation error
Java 7将出现编译错误
so now we're going to verify it with the
所以现在我们要用
animal sniffer
动物嗅探器
maven plugin
Maven插件
again we have built failure in reason is
再次，我们建立失败的原因是
that the the completion succeeded and
完成成功，并且
afterwards the animals information
之后的动物信息
begins jack and it detects that this
开始杰克，它检测到这
java.util this dream is not known same
java.util这个梦想是未知的
count 40 for each with consumer
每个消费者数40
and then we have the JDK 9 or Java 9
然后我们有了JDK 9或Java 9
option where we can specify it as a
选项，我们可以将其指定为
release so now we do May 15 for Phi and
发布，所以我们现在在5月15日为Phi和
we specified in this case with the
我们在这种情况下用
property may have a compiler release and
该属性可能具有编译器版本，并且
again it's comparing complaining about
再次比较抱怨
the failure in the code so the solutions
代码中的失败，所以解决方案
which are already there available in
那里已经有
maven there's now probably a better
专家现在可能有更好的选择
solution in Java 9 now let's see
现在让我们看看Java 9中的解决方案
something about forward compatibility
关于前向兼容性
suggests we have something like this we
建议我们有这样的东西我们
have a specific code and we want to do
有一个特定的代码，我们想做
some calculations and in case of Java 8
一些计算，对于Java 8
we can use the data API because it's
我们可以使用数据API，因为它
very strong and otherwise we can do it
非常强大，否则我们可以做到
based on this but it's more work to do
基于此，但还有更多工作要做
it so and we want to be able to run this
这样，我们希望能够运行此
code with Java 7 there are two options
Java 7中的代码有两种选择
in this case so either you are going to
在这种情况下，您要么
compile it with JDK 8 or you can compile
可以使用JDK 8进行编译，也可以进行编译
it with jdk 1.7 but use reflection to I
它与JDK 1.7，但对我使用反射
use the date/time API
使用日期/时间API
for this there's the Nautilus jar files
为此，有Nautilus jar文件
a new jib to 3/8 and for those who were
一个新的臂架到3/8，对于那些
yesterday with the session from Allen
昨天与艾伦的会议
Bateman there was already an example
贝特曼已经有一个例子
about it and this is how such as Josh
关于它，这就是乔希
structure could look like so we have a
结构看起来像这样，所以我们有一个
jar root it has the claws a b c and d
jar根有爪abc和d
and then you have a meta-inf with
然后你有一个元信息
directory versions and in this case 8
目录版本，在这种情况下为8
and 9 with specific implementations of
和9的具体实现
those classes of course java 8 is not
这些类当然不是Java 8
aware of a multi release jar so it's
知道多释放罐，所以
only 40 X example to understand what
只有40倍的例子来了解
it's doing what it is doing so if we
如果我们正在做它正在做的事情
would translate this back to source
会将其翻译回源
files it would probably look something
文件可能看起来会有些东西
like this
像这样
so we have the project root we have
所以我们有项目根
source main Java with those Java files
带有这些Java文件的源Java主代码
for a b c and d and we have a source
对于abc和d，我们有一个来源
main java 8 for a and b and a sort of
Java 8的a和b以及一种
main and java 9 so this would be if you
主要和Java 9因此，如果您
have only one maven project one jar this
只有一个Maven项目一个罐子
will work with maven without any without
将与Maven一起工作
any problems because of the execution
由于执行而引起的任何问题
blocks you can specify but most IDs will
您可以指定的代码块，但大多数ID
complain about it because they can only
抱怨它，因为他们只能
use one version of java per made project
每个制作的项目使用一个Java版本
so we've been thinking about it and we
所以我们一直在考虑，我们
came with this solution a multi module
该解决方案附带了一个多模块
project it is ideally friendly and you
项目它非常理想，您
can already use it right now so we have
现在可以使用它了
in the root we have a military space
从根本上讲，我们拥有军事空间
with the ABC and d f-- versions of Java
Java的ABC和df--版本
for a motor race 8 same sort of in Java
Java 8的赛车比赛
as we are used for 9 as well and in the
因为我们也用于9
end we have an assembly descriptor which
最后我们有一个汇编描述符
assembles all those goes back to one jar
组装所有那些回到一个罐子
file
文件
you can download this example from the
您可以从
link below so let's see how that works
下面的链接，让我们看看它是如何工作的
so here
所以在这里
here we have the military's route with
在这里，我们有军队的路线
sub-modules Nash Cassie this is the base
子模块Nash Cassie，这是基础
with Java 7 Java 8 and the first no
与Java 7 Java 8和第一个没有
Felicia Eclipse I'm using it's not aware
我正在使用的Felicia Eclipse不知道
of Java 9 yet so it's complaining about
Java 9的诞生，所以它在抱怨
this code this is a specific methods
这段代码这是一个具体方法
that has been introduced in Java 9 so
在Java 9中已经引入
for that reason it's complaining about
因此，它在抱怨
it so let's execute it so I'm doing math
所以让我们执行它，所以我在做数学
cleanest all and most of the time I
大多数时候我最干净
would say never use math clean install
会说从不使用数学全新安装
unless you know what you're doing and
除非你知道自己在做什么，
here we go build success so the reason I
在这里，我们建立成功，所以我的原因
did
做了
maven clean install instead of may
Maven全新安装而不是可能
verify is because I want to show you
验证是因为我想给你看
that the install is skipped in this case
在这种情况下跳过安装
and that will also be in case of the
而且在
deploy so the the sub products will not
部署，以便子产品不会
end up in any of the repositories
最终出现在任何存储库中
so let's have a look at the output if we
所以让我们看一下输出
run it with Java 7 it will be simply
使用Java 7运行它将非常简单
base for Java 8 of course the same
Java 8的基础当然相同
because it is not aware yet of the most
因为它还不了解最多
released jar in the case of Java 9 it
在Java 9中发布了jar
will be from base mine and we have if we
将来自基础矿山，如果我们有
have a look at the code you can
看一下你可以的代码
recognize it that's here it does s gets
认识到它在这里得到
which is mine
这是我的
so it does pick up the right class and
所以它确实选对了课程
this is the content of this not Aires
这不是这个Aires的内容
jar so you recognize here the folders 8
jar，以便您在此处识别文件夹8
&amp; 9 we have an a for 8 a 4 9 and here we
＆9我们有一个8 8 4 9的a
have the base a first
首先拥有基地
like I said this is just proof of
就像我说的，这只是证明
concept to start with and we're thinking
概念开始，我们正在思考
about several improvements we want to
关于我们想要的一些改进
apply we want to introduce new acting
应用我们要介绍新的表演
type something like sabji R which
输入类似sabji R的名称
doesn't do any install or deployments we
不进行任何安装或部署
also have to think about dependencies
还必须考虑依赖关系
for instance if you have the Java 8
例如，如果您有Java 8
module multi module there can be
可以有多个模块
specific dependencies there and we need
那里有特定的依赖关系，我们需要
to put them in a new dedicate profile
将它们放入新的专用配置文件中
and of course we want to get rid of the
当然，我们要摆脱
assembly descriptor it should work out
程序集描述符应该解决
of the box that's the future so we're
未来的盒子，所以我们
still in still work in progress now
仍在进行中
let's go to material runtime images as
让我们转到重要的运行时映像
you probably already know and that the
您可能已经知道，
whole full structure has changed and
整个完整结构已经改变，
what's the impact for a maven in this
这对行家有什么影响
case well some projects depends on tools
好吧，一些项目取决于工具
top jar and that has been removed but
顶罐，它已被删除，但
most of the mave plugins are already
大多数mave插件已经
aware of that and they have several
意识到这一点，他们有几个
scenarios to work to cope with such
应对这种情况的方案
situations one project we worked on had
我们工作的一个项目的情况
to do with custom doctor context that
与自定义医生上下文有关
requires toast OTR and we had to do this
需要烤面包OTR，我们必须这样做
fix at profile and just say that in case
修正个人资料，以防万一
that it's the JDK is below 9 so this
那是JDK在9以下
means 9 not included in that case you
表示在这种情况下不包括9
can use this tools dot you are picked up
可以使用此工具将您接起
from the system path
从系统路径
and this is actually actually quite cool
这实际上很酷
because maven we as a project want to
因为行家我们作为一个项目想要
get rid of this system scope and with
摆脱这个系统范围和
Java 9 that path is there looking good
Java 9那条路看起来不错
mmm
嗯
now let's go finally to the module
现在让我们最后进入模块
system itself which has been changed in
系统本身已更改
a nutshell we have a in in in in in
简而言之，我们在
perspective of the format so we have
格式的角度，所以我们有
this module info Java file and it has
此模块信息Java文件，它具有
several dis content you can specify the
您可以指定几个不同的内容
exposed packages and you also can
暴露的包，你也可以
specify the required modules for both
指定两者所需的模块
Build time and run time and you can
建立时间和运行时间，您可以
specify usage and implementations of
明确说明的用法和实现
server SBI's so this is an example which
服务器SBI，所以这是一个例子
is at this time on still on the internet
目前仍在上网
but as you might see is it is still
但您可能会发现它仍然是
talking about public and static some go
谈论公共和静态一些
to dive in the request part which is
潜入请求部分
closely related to Maiden dependencies
与少女的依赖关系密切
so yesterday when I heard that the talk
所以昨天当我听到谈话
about from Alan about this is that the
关于艾伦，这是关于
requires model modifier public is
需要模型修改器public is
probably going to be transitive so I had
可能会传递，所以我有
to change the title this morning the
今天早上要更改标题
rest is what I said is it was already
剩下的就是我说过的
comparable with transitive
可比的
it is actually a hint for other projects
这实际上是对其他项目的提示
using this jar as a dependency so it has
使用这个罐子作为依赖，所以它有
no effect on the project you are working
对您正在工作的项目没有影响
on actually maven best practice is don't
实际上行之有效的最佳实践是
trust transitive dependencies always
始终信任传递依赖
specify the dependencies for every class
指定每个类的依赖项
you are using and the reason for this is
您正在使用，其原因是
suppose I have a project that uses
假设我有一个使用
spring spring uses Commons logging and
spring spring使用Commons日志记录和
for that reason Commons logging is
因此，Commons Logging是
available on the class path so I can use
在课程路径上可用，所以我可以使用
it in my project spring decides to drop
在我的项目中，春天决定放弃
comments logging and I just simply
评论日志，我只是
update spring just by upgrading spring
通过升级spring来更新spring
the Commons logging here is lost and I
在这里记录下公地的遗失，我
will get compilation errors or even
会得到编译错误甚至
runtime errors so for that reason we say
运行时错误，因此我们说
always specify the dependency for every
始终为每个对象指定依赖项
use class however I was talking to many
使用课程，但是我在和很多人交谈
Chong yesterday and she said in this
昨天冲，她在这说
case this will only happen when spring
情况只会在春天发生
has set transitive on Commons logging
在Commons日志记录中设置了传递
but if it is not exposed on the method
但如果方法未公开
they should never do that the other one
他们不应该那样做
you noticed is static or I saw a mailing
您注意到它是静态的，或者我看到一封邮件
is it there's a proposal to change that
有没有建议要改变这一点
to optional which is comparable with
到与
method and dependency optional
方法和依赖项可选
I'm not sure if everybody is aware of
我不确定所有人是否都知道
the optional tack I think most of you
我想你们大多数人都可以选择
probably will use something like
可能会使用类似
provided but it's not the same okay at
提供，但在这里不一样
Build time there's no difference
建立时间没有区别
difference they are both available on
两者都可以使用
the class path but at run time there's a
类路径，但在运行时有一个
huge difference in case of provided you
为您提供巨大的差异
can expect that that gr is available so
可以期待gr可用
for instance the surface API but
例如表面API，但
optional might be available so for
可选的，因此
instance the springboard dependencies
实例跳板依赖性
so let's have a look at the use cases we
让我们来看看用例
know so on the left side we have a
知道在左侧，我们有一个
classic project and on the right side we
经典项目，在右侧，我们
have assortment Java which has also a
有各种各样的Java也有
module info you can of course also have
您当然可以拥有的模块信息
a module info on the toes source tests
脚趾源测试中的模块信息
Java but that's not supported yes and
Java，但是不支持
I'm also wondering if it makes sense to
我也想知道是否有意义
put a motor info file there so what's
把电机信息文件放在那里
going to happen with the medical pilot
将会与医学飞行员发生
plug-in well in case there's a module
如果有模块可以很好地插入
info file it will automatically switch
信息文件，它将自动切换
to multi path for you so you don't have
到你的多路径，所以你没有
to configure something for yourself to
为自己配置一些东西
use I use the module path in case of the
使用我在以下情况下使用模块路径
test compile and MAIF compiler plug-in
测试编译和MAIF编译器插件
will switch to module path for the main
将切换到主模块的路径
sources and for the class path for the
源和类路径
test sources so let's see that in action
测试源，让我们看看实际情况
I was thinking about projects Multi
我在考虑多项目
multi projects using third party Josh
使用第三方Josh进行多个项目
having a large code base so I thought
我的代码库很大，所以我想
about why not build maven with me and if
关于为什么不跟我建立Maven，以及
we have a look at this this picture this
我们看看这张照片
is the whole graph of Apache maven
是Apache Maven的整体图
wait a minute
等一下
so we're not going to compile the whole
所以我们不会编译整个
project but we're only going to compile
项目，但我们只会编译
this part the setting settings is
这部分的设置设置是
actually a descriptor which is
实际上是一个描述符
generating the code to have Poggio style
生成具有Poggio风格的代码
and it's also creating a reader and a
而且还创造了一个读者和一个
writer for the settings.xml so it's
settings.xml的编写者，因此
actually about the settings.xml the
其实关于settings.xml
build spot is about handling errors and
建立点是关于处理错误和
to combine them all together so you
将它们组合在一起，以便您
don't have to go from one error to the
不必从一个错误转到
order to fix your issues in a
为了解决您的问题
settings.xml and the settings builder
settings.xml和设置构建器
itself it has all kinds of rules in it
它本身具有各种规则
for instance that IDs are unique
例如ID是唯一的
so we're going to compile this part
所以我们要编译这部分
looking good so this is what we did with
看起来不错，所以这就是我们所做的
JDK 9 in the beginning I said well our
在开始JDK 9之前，我对我们说的很好
wish is that it will run with maven 3.0
希望它将与Maven 3.0一起运行
so let's give it a try
所以让我们尝试一下
that's all white again
那又是白色的
again build success so for now it's
再次建立成功，所以现在
looking very very good let's have a look
看起来非常非常好，让我们看一下
at the Maven build sports to see if we
在Maven进行体育运动，看看我们是否
can detect that it is actually using the
可以检测到它实际上是在使用
multipath so we use debug here you can
多路径，所以我们在这里使用调试
see that it is not using the classpath
看到它没有使用classpath
it is only using the multipath and it
它只是使用多路径而已
has added plexus utils and comment
添加了plexus utils和注释
length 3 now let's have a look at what
长度3现在让我们看看
just compiled us
刚刚编译了我们
again ready
再次准备
so now we have a combination of class
所以现在我们有一个类的组合
path and multipath so the jars we
路径和多路径，所以罐子我们
already had during the compile are again
在编译过程中已经有了
on a module path but in this case on a
在模块路径上，但在这种情况下
class path is J units and Empress pore
班级路径是J单位和皇后毛孔
so this is all just based on if there's
所以这全是基于
a module info file or not
是否提供模块信息文件
so nothing you have to do about it how
所以你不必做任何事情
to discover the module name well I hope
我希望能很好地发现模块名称
that once the module names are published
一旦模块名称发布
that there's a little documentation
有一些文档
about it however I also hope that maven
关于这个但是我也希望那个行家
central or any other repository manages
中央或任何其他存储库管理
will provide that kind of information as
将提供这种信息作为
well but right now what I've done is
好吧，但现在我要做的是
I've improved the maven in Tennessee
我改善了田纳西州的行家
plug-in and in this case the lisko which
插件，在这种情况下是lisko，
will show you the module names for all
将为您显示所有模块的名称
those dependencies so in this case maven
这些依赖关系，所以在这种情况下，Maven
dependency plug-in is still the snapshot
依赖插件仍然是快照
I've haven't released it yet call the
我尚未发布它，请致电
list goal on a specific module
列出特定模块上的目标
and as you can see we have here the GRU
如您所见，我们这里有GRU
body an artifact ID and the module name
主体工件ID和模块名称
in this case is common slang and 4j
在这种情况下是普通语和4j
units the motor memory is jailed in this
电机存储器在此被监禁的单位
case it is actually using exactly the
实际使用的是
same code as what a of mine is using to
与我使用的相同的代码
resolve the name of other modules and if
解析其他模块的名称，如果
there's already module info file inside
里面已经有模块信息文件
the gr it will use that dead name so for
gr它将使用该死名，因此
those who are library builders or
那些是图书馆建设者或
framework builders or maven plug-in
框架构建器或Maven插件
builders the lower the version of Java
构建者降低Java版本
are the more projects you can use it
您可以使用更多的项目吗
however that also means that you there
但是那也意味着你在那里
are less job features that you can use
可以使用的工作功能较少
can we add module info in this case yes
我们可以在这种情况下添加模块信息吗？
we can the module info will be ignored
我们可以忽略模块信息
if you are using Java 8 or less however
如果您使用的是Java 8或更低版本
there's a trigger there's a small issue
有一个触发因素，有一个小问题
with it the module fo has to be compiled
使用它，必须编译模块fo
with - release 9 and all the other
与-版本9和所有其他
sources have to be compiled with source
源必须与源一起编译
target below 9 so we have to call the
目标低于9，因此我们必须将
maiden of the Java C twice so there are
Java C的少女，所以有两次
several several solutions for death we
几种死亡的解决方法
could separate it in source force so for
可以将其分开来，以便
instance source main Java and short main
实例源主Java和短主
jigsaw what that would mean that we only
拼图意味着我们只
have death motive info file in the
在中具有死亡动机信息文件
jigsaw folder not really nice it would
拼图文件夹不是很好吗
be much nicer if we could keep it all
如果我们能保留所有这些，那就更好了
together in the short name Java same a
简称Java在一起
bit like the naughty release GRE
有点像调皮的GRE
recently you will have to require a
最近，您将需要
multi module maven multimodal projects
多模块Maven多模式项目
we are probably going to suggest to use
我们可能会建议使用
two executions blocks and in the first
两个执行块，在第一个
one you say explicitly only compile the
你说的一个只编译
motor
发动机
info with nine and in the other case in
信息与九，在另一种情况下在
the other case excludes module info and
另一种情况不包括模块信息和
compile it with another version of Java
使用其他版本的Java进行编译
I've been working on
我一直在努力
mave compiler pledgee plugin magic to do
mave编译器承诺插件魔术
it out of the box I didn't like it so
开箱即用，我不喜欢它
I'm going to follow for that now let's
我现在要关注的是
talk a bit about dependencies and class
谈谈依赖和类
paths and the reason is that this is how
路径，原因是这就是
the class path order works in in case of
类路径顺序在以下情况下有效
Nathan for a project it will first
内森（Nathan）对于一个项目，它将首先
select all the direct dependencies next
选择所有直接依赖项
it will go for the first level in direct
它将直接进入第一级
dependencies then the second and so on
然后是第二个依存关系，依此类推
and so on and so on for locating a class
等等，以此类推
it will iterate over this class path in
它将遍历该类路径
the same order and first match wins this
相同的顺序和第一个比赛将赢得这场比赛
will change in case of a module path you
如果您使用模块路径，它将更改
can think of that pictures are mapped to
可以想到图片被映射到
a specific module in case there are
一个特定的模块，如果有
duplicate packages there will be an
重复的包裹将有一个
exception thrown locating a class is now
现在定位类抛出异常
quite simple just pick your packages key
很简单，只需选择您的包裹钥匙
it will find the module and it will get
它会找到模块，它将得到
that class from that module
该模块中的该类
now there's a small gotcha and that's
现在有一个小陷阱，那就是
about the dependency excludes the Java C
关于依赖项不包括Java C
has an option where you can say limit
有一个可以说限制的选项
modules and you have to specify all the
模块，您必须指定所有
module names you want to exclude from
您要从中排除的模块名称
this execution however the name of the
这个执行但是名称
module is inside the gr and maven
模块在gr和maven内部
excludes those dependencies already up
排除那些已经存在的依赖
front so there's no need to download
前端，因此无需下载
those from or jar and/or jar so if in
那些来自或罐子和/或罐子的东西，如果在
case you have an exclude we probably
如果您有排除对象，我们可能
have to download the world plus a bit
必须下载世界加上一点
more because we have to know which
更多，因为我们必须知道
motives we have to exclude so there's no
我们必须排除动机，所以没有
solution yet for that and the workaround
解决方案尚未解决
is to specify it yourself in the
是自己在
arguments of the configuration so are we
配置的参数，我们也是
there yet no this is a list of all the
还没有这是所有的清单
topics which are waiting for a proposal
正在等待提案的主题
and there are some related to maven and
并且有一些与Maven有关，
they are waiting for an answer for it
他们正在等待答案
for instance the maven shade plug-in it
例如maven shade插件
is plug-in which can make an uber drier
是可以使干燥机更干燥的插件
which means that it will just unpack all
这意味着它只会解开所有包装
the jars combined it's as one the
罐子组合在一起
problem is that if we would merge the
问题是，如果我们将合并
module info files it would break
可能会破坏的模块信息文件
encapsulation because it's not aware
封装，因为它不知道
anymore which packages are of your own
不再是你自己的包了
VR and we also have to think about
VR，我们还必须考虑
relocation relocation is about shifting
搬迁是关于转移
or renaming the package name so this is
或重命名包名称，因此
an issue which still really quite an
这个问题仍然非常
answer there's something else that's a
回答还有其他的东西
bit too fast the animal sniffer now
现在动物嗅探器太快了
there's not anymore just one huge
不再只有一个巨大的
runtime which we can verify with
我们可以验证的运行时
signatures so what do we have to do do
签名，所以我们该怎么做
we have to do it for module
我们必须为模块做
or is it still requires now that we have
还是现在仍然需要
to - release our option it's still a
-释放我们的选择，它仍然是
question that's a request an answer
问题是请求答案
oh that's optimum team so now the
哦，那是最佳团队，所以现在
question for you is my project job and
您的问题是我的项目工作，
I'm ready one of the first questions you
我已经准备好您的第一个问题
have to answer yourself is am I using
必须回答自己是我在用吗
internal classes and for that we've
内部类，为此
created the Maven jaidev's plugin it was
创建了Maven jaidev的插件
released about a year ago and it was
大约一年前发布了
during Java 1 when I noticed that the
在Java 1期间，当我注意到
the slides of the jigsaw team suddenly
拼图团队的幻灯片突然间
mentioned this plug-in and it wasn't
提到了这个插件，但不是
released yet so we did it quite fast and
发布了，所以我们很快完成了
the official release was during the java
官方发布是在Java期间
one and I will show you how that works
一个，我将向您展示其工作原理
so what I'm going to do is am Ava
所以我要做的是阿娃
compile
编译
so I have the class files because Jade
所以我有课程文件，因为玉
EPS uses the classes and not the sources
EPS使用类别而不是来源
and in this case it's using the maven
在这种情况下，它使用的是行家
artifact module
工件模块
so now we have a huge list and you can
所以现在我们有一个庞大的清单，您可以
see the the mapping of all the packages
查看所有包的映射
so in this case the org that she made an
所以在这种情况下，她让
artifact package is the classes inside
神器包是里面的类
that is are using all these packages and
正在使用所有这些软件包，并且
here you can see where several packages
在这里你可以看到几个包
belong to in this case there are no
在这种情况下属于
there's no usage of any internal classes
没有使用任何内部类
from Java but of course we want to see
从Java，但我们当然希望看到
that as well so the jeddak's begin also
吉达也开始了
has an integration test for it so again
对其进行了集成测试
I will go into that integration test and
我将进行集成测试，
run math compiled and verified with the
运行数学编译和验证
JDK internals go
JDK内部知识
and we see failure in this case you see
在这种情况下，我们看到失败
that some misc
一些杂项
it's marked as Angelica internal API and
它被标记为当归内部API，
this already breaks the build so this is
这已经破坏了构建，所以这是
something you can do already right now
您现在已经可以做的事情
just add the jeddak's plug-in to your
只需将jeddak的插件添加到您的
own file and let it check your code over
自己的文件，让它检查您的代码
and over again during our built just to
在我们的建造过程中
see if your product is Java now ready
看看您的产品现在是否支持Java
the other thing is do I have duplicates
另一件事是我有重复吗
and you can verify that with the
您可以使用
enforcer maven enforce plugin and inside
强制执行器maven强制执行插件和内部
the Nathan force plugin specify this
Nathan强制插件指定此
rule then duplicate classes and in case
然后规则重复类，以防万一
you want to use specific job 9 features
您想使用特定的作业9功能
upgrade the plugins to that specific
将插件升级到特定的
version
版
we all have to pick on the eye at the
我们都必须选择
end please okay so the attachment for
结束请好，所以附件
project still has tasks list most
项目仍然有任务清单最多
features should already work with maven
功能应该已经可以使用Maven
3 that we already notice that although
3我们已经注意到，尽管
some require method 3.3 that one due to
有些需要方法3.3，因为
the improved tool change support and
改进的工具更换支持和
that probably has to do with when we
这可能与我们何时
have the module info inside the source
在源代码中包含模块信息
main Java and we want to compile it with
主Java，我们想用
an older version of Java that will
Java的较旧版本
require to change a large number of
需要更换大量
features are already developed but they
功能已经开发，但它们
are not you released yet and we also
你还没被释放，我们也
have to write several recipes for the
必须写一些食谱
maven way so something this is something
专家的方式所以这是某事
you all should know that the module info
你们都应该知道模块信息
Java triggers if the module path will be
Java触发模块路径是否为
used or if the class path will be used
使用或是否将使用类路径
in case of test compile it will use both
在测试编译的情况下，它将同时使用
motive path and class path in case
动机路径和阶级路径
there's a module info file in dark
黑暗中有一个模块信息文件
glasses and again in case your project
眼镜，以防万一您的项目
will fill with Java nano jigsaw is
将充满Java纳米拼图是
probably because of the usage of
可能是因为
internal API or duplicate exported
内部API或重复导出
practice so here's the information you
练习，这就是你的信息
can find
可以找到
and I will publish this this slice as
我将把这个片段发布为
well so and that's it for now give it a
好吧，现在就给它一个
try I would say and thank you very much
尝试我会说，非常感谢你
so are there any questions please come
所以有什么问题请来
to the front so everybody can hear it
放在前面，这样每个人都可以听到
they've come to hear so because they're
他们来听是因为他们
also filming it yes then you talk about
也拍它是的然后你谈论
duplicate band to play pluses then force
复制乐队演奏加号，然后强制
plugin my question is like it only
插件我的问题是只喜欢它
checks my own build classes like my
检查我自己的构建类，例如
application classes or it also checks
应用程序类或它也检查
duplicate classes in the third-party
第三方中的重复类
jars our typical use cases in big
大大影响了我们的典型用例
applications we have seen or as a
我们已经看到的应用或
developer you don't know sometimes you
有时你不知道的开发者
have a dependency on different versions
依赖于不同的版本
of third-party jars and it brings two
第三方罐子，它带来了两个
versions of the same implementation and
相同实现的版本和
most of the time it conflicts and yes
大多数情况下它是冲突的，是的
gets error in the runtime so to avoid
在运行时出错，以避免
that one does it really mean that way or
那真的是那样吗？
just a us exactly what's this for this
只是我们，这到底是什么
enforce rule is the way it's verifying
强制规则是其验证方式
that you don't have any duplicates
你没有任何重复
classes okay including third-party jobs
好的课程，包括第三方工作
exactly perfect especially especially
尤其是特别完美
those third-party jars so all the
这些第三方罐子
transitive tree please come to the front
传递树请来到前面
I will
我会
so are there any plans to merge maven
所以有合并Maven的计划吗
dependencies with the module
与模块的依赖
dependencies in module info or do I need
模块信息中的依赖项还是我需要
to specify both maven dependencies and
同时指定Maven依赖项和
the module dependencies there's no
模块依赖性没有
difference between your just specifying
您刚才指定的区别
maven dependencies as you are used to if
习惯于Maven依赖
you are talking about do I have to write
你在说我要写吗
my own module info file yes probably and
我自己的模块信息文件可能是
merge them you're talking about
合并您正在谈论的它们
generating the part of the module info
生成模块信息的一部分
file the problem is that it's only a
文件的问题是，这只是一个
specific part of that file the other
该文件的特定部分，另一个
things like the let me go back to export
像这样让我回去出口
yes
是
right here so yes the requires parts can
就在这里，是的，需要的零件可以
be generated but all the others cannot
被产生，但其他所有不能
so then we have Church are we going to
所以我们有教堂
generate half of a file the other way
用另一种方式生成文件的一半
around is not possible because where are
周围不可能，因为在哪里
those jars coming from you don't you
那些来自你的罐子不是吗
cannot specify calculate the path to a
无法指定计算到的路径
specific artifact purely based on the
特定的工件完全基于
name of the module that's the whole
整个模块的名称
problem
问题
hi notations is there's actually one one
嗨，符号实际上是一个
developer is trying to work with
开发人员正在尝试与
annotations to see if that's going to
注释以查看是否要
work it's it's a proof-of-concept he's
工作是他的概念证明
working on it thank you for the talk I
努力工作，谢谢你的演讲
was I wasn't completely following with
是我没有完全关注
how banning duplicate classes relates to
禁止重复的类有何关系
being ready for JDK 9 okay the problem
准备好使用JDK 9可以了
is in case you have two jars which have
如果你有两个罐子
duplicate classes so I know for instance
复制类，所以我知道例如
I think it's it's JBoss it sometimes
我想有时候是JBoss
just has an uber jar which has and
只是有一个带有
there's also some kind of JRR 250 I
还有某种JRR 250 I
think and they are using exactly the
认为，他们正在使用
same classes in that case you cannot
在那种情况下，你不能
start it with a Java 9 because of the
用Java 9来启动它
automotive it will export everything so
汽车它将出口一切，所以
ok so that's not specifically maven
好，那不是专门的专家
related no it's just Java 9 it's Jeff
相关的不只是Java 9是Jeff
and I'm really it's a sickly yes sorry
我真的是病得很对不起
any other questions okay thank you very
还有其他问题吗，非常感谢
much
许多